{
  "topics": [
    {
      "id_topic": "A",
      "topic_name": "English",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id_question": "A1",
          "question": "What is number after two?",
          "id_solution": 1,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "three"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "one"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "zero"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "five"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "A2",
          "question": "What is number before two?",
          "id_solution": 2,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "three"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "one"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "zero"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "five"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "A3",
          "question": "What is two divided by one?",
          "id_solution": 1,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "two"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "one"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "zero"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "five"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "A4",
          "question": "What is number after three?",
          "id_solution": 3,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "three"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "one"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "four"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "five"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "A5",
          "question": "What is number after zero?",
          "id_solution": 2,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "three"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "one"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "zero"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "five"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id_topic": "B",
      "topic_name": "Japanese",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id_question": "B1",
          "question": "Konnichiwa means?",
          "id_solution": 1,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "Hello"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "Bye"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "Nice to meet you"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "Good Evening"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "B2",
          "question": "Konbanwa means?",
          "id_solution": 4,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "Hello"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "Bye"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "Nice to meet you"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "Good Evening"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "B3",
          "question": "Douzoyoroshiku means?",
          "id_solution": 3,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "Hello"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "Bye"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "Nice to meet you"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "Good Evening"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "B4",
          "question": "Jaane means?",
          "id_solution": 2,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "Hello"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "Bye"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "Nice to meet you"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "Good Evening"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id_question": "B5",
          "question": "Mataashita means?",
          "id_solution": 2,
          "choices": [
            {
              "id_choice": 1,
              "choice": "Hello"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 2,
              "choice": "See you tomorrow"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 3,
              "choice": "Nice to meet you"
            },
            {
              "id_choice": 4,
              "choice": "Good Evening"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
